import {
  CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
  KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
  TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
  TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
  VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
  LessonsContentDictType
} from './SharedVariables'

export const Content: LessonsContentDictType = {
  'ガ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ガ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'が',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ガ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'が',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ギ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ギ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぎ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ギ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぎ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'グ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'グ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぐ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'グ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぐ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ゲ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ゲ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'げ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ゲ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'げ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ゴ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ゴ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ご',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ゴ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ご',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ザ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ザ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ざ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ザ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ざ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ジ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ジ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'じ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ジ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'じ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ズ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ズ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ず',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ズ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ず',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ゼ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ゼ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぜ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ゼ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぜ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ゾ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ゾ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぞ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ゾ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぞ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ダ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ダ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'だ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ダ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'だ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ヂ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ヂ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぢ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ヂ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぢ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ヅ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ヅ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'づ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ヅ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'づ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'デ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'デ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'で',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'デ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'で',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ド-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ド',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ど',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ド',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ど',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'バ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'バ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ば',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'バ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ば',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ビ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ビ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'び',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ビ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'び',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ブ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ブ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぶ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ブ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぶ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ベ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ベ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ベ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'べ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'べ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ボ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ボ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぼ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ボ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぼ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'パ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'パ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぱ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'パ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぱ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ピ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ピ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぴ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ピ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぴ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'プ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'プ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぷ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'プ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぷ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぺ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぺ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぺ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぺ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぺ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ポ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ポ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ぽ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ポ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ぽ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'アルバイト-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'アルバイト',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Part Time Job, Part-Time Job',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Part Time Job, Part-Time Job',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'アルバイト',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'アルバイト',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'part time job',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          },
          {
            answer: 'part-time Job',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'テレビ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'テレビ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Television',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Television',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'テレビ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'テレビ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'television',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ドラマ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ドラマ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Drama',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Drama',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ドラマ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ドラマ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'drama',
            distanceToAllow: 1
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ジュース-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ジュース',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Juice',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Juice',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ジュース',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ジュース',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'juice',
            distanceToAllow: 1
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'スーパー-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'スーパー',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Supermarket',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Supermarket',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'スーパー',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'スーパー',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'supermarket',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'メーク-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'メーク',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Makeup, Make-up',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Makeup, Make-up',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'メーク',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'メーク',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'makeup',
            distanceToAllow: 2
          },
          {
            answer: 'make-up',
            distanceToAllow: 2
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'パソコン-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'パソコン',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Personal Computer, PC',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Personal Computer, PC',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'パソコン',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'パサコン',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'Personal Computer',
            distanceToAllow: 5
          },
          {
            answer: 'pc',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  }
}

export default Content
